activemailorder.com 2016-11-30

# Privacy Policy

Active Ride Shop would like to thank you for your support and wants you to know that your privacy is very important to us. This privacy policy is provided to explain how information is collected on our website and how that information is handled once it has been collected. Please note that this privacy policy may change at any time. While using the ActiveRideShop.com website you accept the terms and conditions described in this privacy policy. For the latest changes to our privacy policy click the privacy link on our website at any time.

### Active Ride Shop Registration

Personal information is gathered by Active Ride Shop during the order check out process. During the check out process, your name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, fax number, credit card information, and information about your interests in and use of various products, programs, and services are collected. Your account user name and password are collected at this time as well. Please note that your user name is your email address and you may create your own unique password. If you forget your password you can request to have your password emailed to your email address. For security reasons, Active Ride Shop does not store sensitive credit card information on our servers. To view your account history click My Account at any time to view your Active Ride Shop order history and track the status of your orders placed online. In order to view the information in the My Account section of the site you must first log in using your username and password. Remember your user name is your email address. Personal information is also gathered by Active Ride Shop when you request a catalog. When a catalog is requested we gather your name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, fax number, and information about your interests in and use of various products, programs, and services. If at any time you would like to be removed from our email list please send an email to remove@activerideshop.com and type Remove in the subject line.

### Updating Personal Information

Log on to ActiveRideShop.com and click My Account to update your personal information online. You can also call 800.588.3911 and an Active Ride Shop sales representative can change your information for you. You must first state your user name and password, prior to any change of information. If you have lost or do not remember your password please send an email from the email account/address you used to register. We will only send password information to the email address listed under the account/address. Password information cannot be given out over the phone.

### Information Usage

The information collected during registration is used to primarily to process and ship your order and/or catalog. Your account information is maintained privately on our secure web servers. Occasionaly, unless otherwise requested during the check out process, Active Ride Shop may share information about our customer's with affiliated companies and other reputable third party vendors in order to enhance the service we provide. Active Ride Shop requires this information be handled securely and responsibly. Active Ride Shop does not sell, share, or rent email addresses and does not condone unsolicited email.

Active Ride Shop will disclose any information we maintain when required to do so by law, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena. We also may disclose such information in response to a law enforcement agency's request.

Remember, Active Ride Shop will not use or transfer the personal information provided to us in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you with an opportunity to opt out of these unrelated uses.

### PROMOTIONAL OFFERS, CONTESTS, & SWEEPSTAKES

Active reserves the right to cancel any transaction due to unauthorized, altered, fraudulent, or ineligible use of discount and to modify or cancel this promotion due to system error or unforeseen problems at any time. Please read the official rules that may accompany each promotion, offer, coupon, discount, contest and/or sweepstakes. Promotional offers and discounts do not apply to gift cards, shipping and handling, or taxes. Discounts will appear upon checkout and may or may not be eligible to be combined with any other offers or discounts. Special offers, coupons, or discounts cannot be used in conjunction with other offers unless specifically stated in offer official rules.

### Cookies

Small text files stored on your computer's hard drive, cookies are used by Active Ride Shop to enhance your shopping experience. Cookies are also used to speed up the browsing experience and web site performance while using the Active Ride Shop web site. They are used to personalize your experience while using our web site. Finally, we also use cookies to remember your information when you come back to our site. This functionality is activated when the remember me check box is clicked. To turn this functionality off simply uncheck the remember me check box.

### The Privacy of Young Skaters

Active Ride Shop does not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13. Children under the age of 13 should have their parents fill out required registration or catalog information.

### Security

The security of the information regarding your order is very important to us. We use the 128-bit Secure Socket Layer protocol to protect the security of your online order information. You can be assured that all sensitive information will be handled with the utmost discretion and security. SSL technology encrypts your order information to protect it from being decoded by anyone other than Active Ride Shop.

Click here to visit our Security section of our website which further explains how you are protected on activerideshop.com

### Questions and Concerns

If you have any question or concerns in regard to our privacy policy please contact Active Ride Shop at:

  * **ActiveRideShop.com**
  * 12178 4th Street
  * Rancho Cucamonga, CA 91730
  * 800-588-3911
  * Outside the US call:
  * 951-934-4200
